{
    "id": "cefb11a567ae4e40b64a823d9bf7f059",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Mia can sing beautifully, and ……………………..",
            "description": "\r\nSo can be used in the structure so + auxiliary verb + subject. This structure is used to add to the sentence before.\r\n",
            "answers": [
                "so her sister can",
                "her sister can also",
                "so can her sister"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "629dbede88ae4c14bddeb0120398547b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have never eaten …………………………. food in my life.",
            "description": "We use so much before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "so much",
                "so many",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "52495e1c87cb406c8e96ad3820314285"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ………………………. children to take care of.",
            "description": "We use so many before plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "so many",
                "so much",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "98910b3d05a04d8290a1bce3d659bd6f"
        },
        {
            "question": "They held the ceremony on a Sunday …………………………… everybody would be able to attend.",
            "description": "The structures so that and in order that are used to talk about purpose.",
            "answers": [
                "so that",
                "in order that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d6384e190a0e4bf7b2e342691aaf7aa8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Send the parcel express so that they ……………………….. it before Friday.",
            "description": "After so that and in order that, we can use a present or future tense to refer to future.",
            "answers": [
                "get",
                "will get",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "36544f7756da45e997a86e22d462239d"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are ………………………. children at the front door.",
            "description": "We use some in affirmative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e5ee850a1faa460d95ed29eb302bbf38"
        },
        {
            "question": "You haven’t got ………………………… manners.",
            "description": "We use any in questions and negative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6fc3931ddf0b4e6bbed24c00ada61833"
        },
        {
            "question": "We met ………………………….. interesting people on holiday.",
            "description": "We use some in affirmative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "some",
                "any",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2cb5cd3edd8b4e1caeeffdf2b2c79fe6"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… people want to go to the movies.",
            "description": "We use some before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1aa575aa4360419995cbb818ce3a6be5"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… us want to go to the movies.",
            "description": "Before a pronoun we use some of.",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Some of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a8d81ee582d34e9ab38d06cd6abafde8"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is little point in doing ………………………… more work now.",
            "description": "Any can be used in affirmative clauses after words like little and hardly.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "some",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c41bbb7d75924005b0e49dd023a0fc95"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is somebody outside who ……………………………. to talk to you.",
            "description": "Somebody usually refers to only one person.",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wants",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fbf97fd697cc46b1a0c1552c9925d6f8"
        }
    ]
}